Regner Raphael Gako

Jr. Software Engineer

WWW.ART 00.ME
ORANGE CALIFORNIA, USA 92868
RAPHAELG2012@GMAIL.COM
7605148024

SUMMARY

Team player full-stack web developer with a can-do attitude, 2+ years experience in web development, phenomenal time management skills, and a strong user focus. Has developed several web apps using the latest technology, and actively participating in open source projects.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, React.js, Angular2, Redux, Express.js, Node.js, Sequelize, Ruby On Rails, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, GIT, Mocha, Chai, Jasmine, Jest, Rspec, AWS

EMPLOYMENT

FEB 2019 - PRESENT

Jr. Software Engineer, Dentca, Torrance California USA

Jr. Software Engineer at Dentca, I am a full stack developer with a little DevOps. My accomplishments so far are:

- Automate deletion of an out of dated record/object on AWS Bucket using bash script that runs on a gitlab runner.
- Maintained and developed sales reports which boost the admin's productivity.
- Created a guided tour on the frontend using angular2 which captures the user's attention and easily navigates the user on the site.
- Implemented a feature to generate shipping labels and save that shipping labels to AWS bucket.

DEC 2016 - PRESENT

Web Developer (Freelance), Chingu, Remote

I've been contributing to open-source projects and also a freelance web developer.

- Improved data visualization and user experience by using D3.js.
- Used Graphql for our API to have an efficient guery.
- Lessen bug reports on production by doing a unit testing using mocha.js and chai.js.
- Migrate JQuery codebase to ReactJs which created reusable and scalable components.
- Built a centralized job searching app using node.js, express.js for REST ful API. MySQL as the database, sequelize.js for ORM, 3 third-party APIs to fetch jobs data, and handlebars.js to view dynamic data.
- Helped wrote test suites using Rspec.
- Helped fixed issue on build process on electron app.

EDUCATION

JUN 2008 - MAR 2012

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, Notre Dame (Philippines)